# Rodrigo Nóbrega

Outsystems Web developer

FullStack Web developer



# Dear Hiring Manager,

After almost 7 years of experience in the manufacturing industry, passing through large multinationals in the automotive sector, I decided to change areas and I found myself with a new challenge. Yes... Today I can consider myself the newest programmer in the field!

In 2020 during the pandemic I got to know the OutSystems lowcode technology, and after a bootcamp I graduated as a web developer. I carried out some case study projects where I managed to develop some skills in technology.

Recently, on 06/2022, I concluded the bootcamp for Le Wagon's FullStack Web Developer in Lisbon. During the course we used several languages as learning, among them... Ruby on rails, html, CSS, Javascript, among other tools. At the end of the course we created a team project, which I was very proud of. An application aimed at communities, where through an in-app currency, you can exchange services with your neighbors.

Take a look...

www.neighbud.me

In this journey I discovered where I want to go to become a great Developer. If you want to chat and talk about future work, just send a message!

Thank you very much for your time and consideration.

Sincerely, odrigo Vobrega



# Rodrigo Nóbrega

Mechanical engineer worked for many years in the manufacture of large automotive multinationals. Today in change of area for IT. On this path that I started a few months ago, I have acquired skills in outsystems and as a FullStack Developer participating in bootcamps.



















#### **SKILLS**

- Ruby on Rails
- Outsystems Web Developer
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- PostgreSQL

- Figma

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English B2
- Portuguese Native

#### **EDUCATION**

- - Le Wagon Lisbon
- Outsystems Web Developer
- Bachelor Mechanical Engineer
- Laureate University Brazil

#### **CONTACT**

- +351 913 660 399

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### O.E.M UTE Chief

**DENSO Portugal** 

(2020 - 2022)

Head of production at the OEM. Working with production planning, Analysis and reporting of KPIs, OEE, scrap and rework. Team and operators management, improvement management through ideas and kaizen.

## **Production Supervisor**

(2015 - 2020)

FCA Fiat Chrysler Automobilis

Production supervisor, with production and process management with lean projects focused on reducing costs and increasing productivity.

# Volleyball Professional Player (2004 - 2013)

Volleyball Professional Player

Professional Volleyball player, having played for major teams in Brazil and Qatar. Champion of many championships, such as Brazilian championship, Paulista champion and vice champion of the Qatar Cup, among other champions

## My Projects and portifolio

Github - https://github.com/rodrigonobrega1 Portfolio - https://personal-eodr.outsystemscloud.com/Home/ LinkedIn - https://linkedin.com/in/rodrigonobrega1/